Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Archives Organization File Additional records
0000-2999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
5956
48 cubic feet
48 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
5743719
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
E. Parker, October 11, 2019
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, October 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of various pamphlets relating to labor and work.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
Automation.; Automobile industry and trade.; Boycotts.; Casual labor.; Child labor.; Coal trade.; Collective bargaining.; Labor disputes.; Economic history.; Vocational education.; Electronic data processing.; Employees--Attitudes.; Discrimination in employment.; Agricultural laborers.; Public contracts.; Collective bargaining -- Government employees.; Hours of labor.; Industrial relations; Job analysis; Job descriptions; Labor laws and legislation; Labor mobility; Labor unions; Labor unions and international relations; Labor unions--Political activity; Free enterprise; Profit-sharing; Railroads; Social security--Law and legislation; Textile industry; Clothing trade; Employees--Training of; Wages; Incentives in industry; Job satisfaction
5743719
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Migratory-Casual Worker, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    By John N. Webb. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What Next for New York's Joads?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Beulah Amidon. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Depression Pioneers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By David Cushman Coyle. Social Problems Number 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Joads in New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Consumers League of New York. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Transient Unemployed, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: "She's a Swell Plane, Give Us More!" More Production, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By War Production Board - A4. Large poster. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Migratory Workers: The Mobile Tenth of American Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Lowry Nelson. Planning Pamphlets No 82. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mexican Farm Labor Program: Consultants Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Glenn E. Garrett; George G. Higgins; Edward J. Thye; Rufus B. von Kleinsmid. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Colorado Tale, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Sol Markoff. Publication No. 406. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Sweatshops In the Sun, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Alexander L. Crosby. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Migrant Farm Labor in Colorado: A Study of Migratory Families, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Howard E. Thomas; Florence Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Migratory Agricultural Labor in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Josiah C. Folsom. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Children of Misfortune: A Study of the Education of Migrant Children, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Shirley E. Greene. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pullman Boycott of 1984: The Problem of Federal Intervention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Colston E. Warne. Subtitled: Problems in American Civilization. Readings Selected by the Department of American Studies, Amherst College. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Boycott and the AFL-CIO Merger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Employers Labor Relations Information Committee, Inc. Part of a magazine called The Communicator (issue No. 17); January 28, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Boycotts: Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Mary R. Heslet. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Case Against Secondary Boycotts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By National Electrical Manufacturers Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Labor Boycott: A Bibliography, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Emanuel Stein; Delia Randall; Jesse Prussin. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: An Industrial Romance of the Rossendale Valley: The Development of the Shoe and Slipper Industries, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Phyllis Cronkshaw. Reprinted from the "Transactions of the Lancashire and Cheshire Antiquarian Society", Vol. LX - 1948. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: World Auto Companies - II. Ford Motor Company; Preparatory Document - VI. IMF World Auto Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By United Auto Workers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United States Automobile Industry Status Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. December 1, 1981. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Administered Prices in the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Walter P. Reuther. Prepared for the Subcommitte on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate; April 3, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Effects of the Defense Program on Employment in the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Sol Swerdloff; E. Eleanor Rings. Manpower Report No. 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Trends: Reporting and Analyzing Developments at the Bargaining Level, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Stanley H. Brams. No. 658; May 31, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: While We Work FOR It Let's Work AT It, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Frederick J. Bell. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Notice to All Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Automobile Labor Board. 3 notice signs stapled together; addressed to Chevrolet Motor Company Gear and Axle Division, Dodge Brothers Corporation, Plymouth Motor Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Automotive Council Statement on Manpower Problems and Their Effect on War Production, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By George Romney. Addressed to the Senate War Investigating Committee; March 9, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Notice to Employees of Various Automobile Plants Regarding Election of Representatives to Act in Dealing with Management and the Labor Group Affiliation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Automotive Labor Board. Folder containing notices to various motor companies. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Statement by L. L. Colbert, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By L. L. Colbert. Addressed to Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate; Thursday, February 6, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report on Detroit Equipment Plants, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Automotive Parts and Equipment Manufacturers, Inc. Series of charts about the plants; December 16, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What "Fringe" Payments Cost, Per Hour, Over and Above Direct Wages in the Automotive Parts Industry and What the "Hidden Payroll" Costs Parts Manufacturing Companies -- Over and Above Direct Wages Paid to Hourly-Rated Factory Workers., Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Automotive and Aviation Parts Manufacturers, Inc. First survey published March 10, 1948; Second survey published April 29, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manufacturer's Responsibility in Distribution, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By M. E. Coyle. May 18, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Why Does the Auto Union Cause So Much Trouble in the Automotive Industry?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By George Romney. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Statement by George Romney, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By George Romney. Addressed to the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate; February 7, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Statement by Harlow H. Curtice on the Relationship of Costs to Prices, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. Addressed to the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, United States Senate; Thursday, January 30, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Outlook for the Automobile Industry, a Talk by M. E. Coyle, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By M. E. Coyle. October 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Preliminary Report on Study of Regularization of Employment and Improvement of Labor Conditions in the Automobile Industry: Appendix C, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By National Recovery Administration. January 23, 1935. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Cybernation: The Silent Conquest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Donald N. Michael. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Automation and Major Technological Change: Impact on Union Size, Structure and Function, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By AFL-CIO. April 22, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Seminar on Manpower Policy and Program: Automation in the Perspective of Long-Term Technological Change, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Robert L. Heilbroner. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Seminar on Manpower Policy and Program: Automation, Skill, and Manpower Predictions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By E. R. F. W. Crossman. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Looks at Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Automation: What Happened to the Hand In the Automat?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By W. Gabriel Carras. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Impact of Automation on American Unionism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Julius Rezler. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Automation, Productivity and Manpower Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Derek Bok. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Background Information on Impact of Automation and Technological Change on Employment and Unemployment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Methods of Adjusting to Automation and Technological Change, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Automation: The Benefits and Problems Incident to Automation and Other Technological Advances, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By The President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy. January 11, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Automation in General Electric: The Human Side of the Story, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Louis Rader. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Steelworkers and Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By United Steelworkers of America. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: American Trade Unions and Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By R. Harle. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Automation and Job Trends, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Council for Technological Advancement. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Automation: Its Impact on Business and Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By John Diebold. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Automation: Technology's New Face, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Jack Rogers. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Automation: A Report to the UAW-CIO Economic and Collective Bargaining Conference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By UAW-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Looks at Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Labor Looks at Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Application of Automation in Europe, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Eric Southwell. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Age of Automation: Its Effects on Human Welfare, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Warner Bloomberg, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Meeting the Problems of Automation through Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By International Association of Machinists. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Impact of Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Walter P. Reuther. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Progress Report Automation Committee, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Armour and Company. June 19, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Automation and Major Technological Change: Collective Bargaining Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Geographical Features of the Automation of Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By David G. Osborn. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Technological Advances and Skilled Manpower Implications for Trade and Industrial Education: An Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Automation and the Bell System, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Selected Bibliography on Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Testimony on Automation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By General Electric. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Why Our Union Welcomes 'Automation' and Opposes 'Featherbedding', Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Edward Swayduck. Transcript of guest speaker, Edward Swayduck's, address to the Economic Club of Detroit; occurred September 25, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Automation and Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Juanita M. Kreps. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Arbitration in Action: The Story of the American Arbitration Association, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Robert Coulson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Arbitration: A Bibliography 1967-1971, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Federal Committee on Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The National Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Apprenticeship: Past and Present, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: A Woman's Guide to Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: A Woman's Guide to Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Sources of Assistance for Recruiting Women for Apprenticeship Programs and Skilled Nontraditional Blue-Collar Work; State and Local Sources of Information and Programs Region V, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. 2 pamphlets stapled together. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Apprentice Training: An Explanation of the Organization, The Administration and the Objectives of the Program of Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Federal Committee on Apprentice Training. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Authorization, Objective, Functions, and Minimum Standards of The Federal Committee on Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Training Apprentices for War and Post-War Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. War Manpower Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Apprenticeship: Information and Experiences in the Development of Industrial Training, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Chamber of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Indentured Apprenticeship: A Discussion of the Procedure for Placing Apprentices Under Agreements, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Report of Conference of General Committee on Apprenticeship for the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. May 16, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Apprentice Training in the Building Trades, 1950-1955, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By John S. McCauley. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Union Participation in Apprenticeship in 32 Selected States and Territories, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Technical Bulletin No. T-132. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Apprenticeship Practice in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Eugene Danaher. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the Aircraft Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Face Sheet on Work Stoppages in the Airline Industry, 1946-70, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. April 9, 1971. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Organization of Farm Labor in The United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Alexander Morin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Changing Technology and Employment in Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By John A. Hopkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining in the Farm Machinery and Equipment Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Fact Sheet on Work Stoppages in the Farm Machinery and Equipment Industry, 1946-69, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. June 15, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Relations in Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Varden Fuller. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The International Landworkers Federation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Leon A. Dale. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Crops and Markets: Wage Rates of Farm Labor Per Month with Board, 1866-1942, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Agriculture. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Underemployment in American Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Arthur Moore. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Impact of Fluctuations in National Income on Agriclutural Wages and Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Howard L. Parsons. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Trade Unions in Agriculture, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Henry William Spiegel. Reprinted from Rural Sociology Vol. 6, No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Mechanization and the Use of Labor on Farms, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Agriculture. May 10, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Numbers, Distribution, Composition, and Employment Status of the Farm Labor Group in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Agriculture. May 8, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Income and Earnings of Farm Laborers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Ernest J. Holcomb. Item is in English.
- Box 1, Folder (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Industrial Absenteeism: The General Motors Experience, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By A. T. Court. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ways of Dealing with Absenteeism as Part of the War Production Drive, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By U.S. War Production Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Manpower Lost: Absence Makes the War Last Longer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Research Papers 8: Three Studies in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Jack Stieber; W. E. J. McCarthy; A. I. Marsh and J. W. Staples. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and the Natoinal Labor Relations Board: A Case Study, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Machinery and Allied Products Institute; Council for Technological Advancement. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A View of the Economic Outlook From the Collective Bargaining Table, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Frank Highton. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining: Will the Private Sector Serve the Public Needs?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Virgil B. Day. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends in Public Assistance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Bureau of research and Statistics. 1933-1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Average General Relief, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Enid Baird; Hugh Brinton. 1933-1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Work relief Experience in the United States, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By John Charnow. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Jobs and Security for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Maxwell Stewart. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Questions and Answers on the WPA, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By john Carmody; F. C. Harrington. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Labor Market and the Unemployed, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Buel Patch. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Re-Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By CIO Department of Research and Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: P.W.A and Industry A Four-year Study of Regenerative Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By Frances Perkins; Isador Lubin. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Problems in American Civilization: Industry-Wide Collective Bargaining, Promise or Menace?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Colston E. Warne. Collection of readings. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industry-Wide Bargaining and Industry-Wide Strikes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Buel W. Patch. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Experience Under National Wage Agreements: The Bituminous Coal and Flint Glass Industries of West Virginia, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Gerald G. Somers. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Free Collective Bargaining Works! A Record of Progress, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By General Motors; UAW-AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The General Motors Proposal for Three Years of Industrial Peace With Security and Economic Progress for GM Hourly Employes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By General Motors. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Sixteen Years of Progress Through Free Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Can the Engineering Student Be Taught to Manage Men?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Society for the Promotion of Engineering Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Teaching Engineering and Business Students to Deal with Men and Manage Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The Teaching of Labor Relations in Engineering Schools, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The University and the Betterment of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By John W. Riegel. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Pioneer Institute of Labor: An Experiment in Understanding, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Spencer Miller, Jr.; Ruth Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Work Training for College Students in Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Donald J. Shank; Kathryn E. Ranck. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Instruction in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Report of the Board of Temporary Trustees of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Cornell University, School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.